export const topick9 = [
  {
    question: 'What maritime festival is held annually in Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Sailors Festival',
      b: "Fishermen's Festival",
      c: 'Sea Festival',
    },
    answer: 'Sea Festival',
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year was the Sea Festival first held in Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: '1801',
      b: '1901',
      c: '2001',
    },
    answer: '1901',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What traditional maritime holiday is celebrated in Ostend in July?',
    options: {
      a: 'Sailors Day',
      b: "Fishermen's Day",
      c: 'Captains Day',
    },
    answer: "Fishermen's Day",
  },
  {
    question:
      'What custom is associated with the start of the fishing season in Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Blessing of the ships',
      b: 'Blessing of the fish',
      c: 'Blessing of the sea',
    },
    answer: 'Blessing of the ships',
  },
  {
    question: 'What maritime holiday is celebrated in Ostend in August?',
    options: {
      a: 'Sailors Day',
      b: "Fishermen's Day",
      c: 'Sea Day',
    },
    answer: 'Sea Day',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What custom is associated with the celebration of Sea Day in Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Parade of ships',
      b: 'Parade of sailors',
      c: 'Parade of fishermen',
    },
    answer: 'Parade of ships',
  },
  {
    question: 'What traditional maritime contest is held in Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Captains Contest',
      b: "Fishermen's Contest",
      c: 'Sailors Contest',
    },
    answer: "Fishermen's Contest",
  },
  {
    question: 'What maritime holiday is celebrated in Ostend in September?',
    options: {
      a: 'Sailors Day',
      b: "Fishermen's Day",
      c: 'Captains Day',
    },
    answer: 'Captains Day',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What custom is associated with the end of the fishing season in Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Blessing of the ships',
      b: 'Blessing of the fish',
      c: 'Blessing of the sea',
    },
    answer: 'Blessing of the fish',
  },
  {
    question: 'What maritime holiday is celebrated in Ostend in October?',
    options: {
      a: 'Sailors Day',
      b: "Fishermen's Day",
      c: 'Captains Day',
    },
    answer: 'Sailors Day',
  },
];
